<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

  <title><![CDATA[Bryan Gamotea's Personal Blog]]></title>
  <link href="http://bryangamotea.github.io/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  <link href="http://bryangamotea.github.io/"/>
  <updated>2014-01-06T19:51:00+08:00</updated>
  <id>http://bryangamotea.github.io/</id>
  <author>
    <name><![CDATA[Bryan Gamotea]]></name>
    
  </author>
  <generator uri="http://octopress.org/">Octopress</generator>

  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Struggle]]></title>
    <link href="http://bryangamotea.github.io/blog/2014/01/06/the-struggle/"/>
    <updated>2014-01-06T19:45:18+08:00</updated>
    <id>http://bryangamotea.github.io/blog/2014/01/06/the-struggle</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><body></p>

<pre><code>&lt;h1&gt;Still Lost&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I'm still finding my way here in octopress. Don't know why my first post looks like that but I'll figure this out, eventually. Anyway, I learned new things again when I'm on the process of configuring this blog. Learning new things makes me feel good. And I hope I can fix whatever error/s I've made.&lt;/p&gt;
</code></pre>

<p></body></p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[My First Post.]]></title>
    <link href="http://bryangamotea.github.io/blog/2014/01/06/my-first-post/"/>
    <updated>2014-01-06T17:37:25+08:00</updated>
    <id>http://bryangamotea.github.io/blog/2014/01/06/my-first-post</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><body></p>

<pre><code>&lt;h1&gt;My First Octopress Post&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;My name is Bryan Nikko G. Gamotea. You can call me Bryan or Nikko for short. I'm a 4th year BSIT student from College of the Immaculate Conception and currently a trainee of Favorite Medium and this is my "STORY". Before we became a trainee here at Favorite Medium, we took a test to see if we are good enough to work for them as trainees. We we're given a .jpeg file(a picture) of a web page and asked to copy it and our work should look exactly like the picture. Fortuntely, we passed(barely) the test. Was the test easy? Yes, it looks easy for me, and I did finished it. But when you look at my code back then, first thing you want to say is "This thing is a mess." Before I got here(Favorite Medium), I consider myself as a "Good" web developer because I can create simple web pages but after I took that test I can now say that I'm not even close to "Good". That was one month ago. Being a trainee here in Favorite Medium is not easy because they will bring out the best in you. After weeks of training there's no doubt that I've improved from "nothing" to "something". Other than developing websites, our other task here is "learn new things". And thaks to that other task, I have learned so many things that I haven't learn in school. One important thing that I've learned here is to go beyond your confort zone because staying in it will not give you anything. Currently I'm way outside of my comfort zone and I can't even see where it is now but one thing for sure is it is nice to live outside of it because here's where the real fun and learning starts. Just want to thank the Favorite Medium family for giving us this opportunity. It's one of the biggest blessing I've recieved. &lt;/p&gt;
</code></pre>

<p></body></p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
</feed>
